Christian Kouris

804 Carnaros • San Clemente, CA • 92672 • 949-444-9796 • christiankouris13@gmail.com

Summary

A hardworking and motivated student who strives for excellence. Currently a student at UC San Diego pursuing a degree in computer engineering, whose goal is to work with experienced engineers that will utilize my background and skills.

Experience

GoVyrl, Intern 6/2019 - 8/2019

- Assisted a team of around 30 developers in creating optimizations to a database of over 1 million customers
- Created multiple development environments using AWS and Buddy-Works
- Created Python scripts to interact with the AWS Parameter Store in order to increase parameter readability

National Honors Society

1/2016 - 6/2017

- Organized fundraisers
- Volunteered at holiday toy drives
- Coordinated horticulture renovation on campus

Education

University of California, San Diego

9/2017 - 3/2021

Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering

Skills

Python	❖ Java	❖ Javascript	❖ React
❖ C	* C++	❖ CSS	♦ HTML
❖ SQL	❖ Problem Solving	❖ Agile Methodologies	❖ Full Stack Engineering
❖ SystemVerilog	❖ Quick Learning	❖ Adaptability	❖ OOP

Projects

- ➤ Built a static website using the basic front-end fundamentals of HTML/CSS/Javascript.
- Worked with a team of 10 to create a full stack web application using Node/React/Express hosted on a Firebase database. The team used agile development to make the application and an MVC model for better security.
- > Created an python AI that can play Gomoku using Monte Carlo Tree Search
- > Created a C++ program that uses UCS in a graph to connect actors through the movies they acted in
- ➤ Used System verilog to create a sha256 encrypter and a 6-tap linear feedback shift register encrypter and decrypter

Certifications

* Learn Java Course	https://www.codecademy.com/profiles/One_Bar/certificates/d3f89367b558583e361640f778191345
* Python (Basic) Certificate	https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/a2d8c7539a25
★ Learn SQL Course	https://www.codecademy.com/profiles/One_Bar/certificates/042a4e5884e3eb6ea1f2a12be6abb851
★ SQL (Basic) Certificate	https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/37aa58332941
★ Learn React Course	https://www.codecademy.com/profiles/One_Bar/certificates/af00e5032d0a68cc84879983f5d8333b